What would it be like for a Telugu village boy to marry a village girl in Kerala?
Food and accommodation
become a big problem when traveling to the Malayalam villages they have given him.  Because
villages don't have proper tourist
infrastructure, while
wandering around a village in Kerala,
a random person I met didn't know my village, did
n't know my name, and didn't even speak my language.  If you cut it, you'll have
accommodation only at their house,
watching football with them, eating food with them, and
watching midnight football matches with the locals. Without even realizing it,
they've all become a family.  They have
become a circle without a circle.  They liked it and
even invited me to the wedding of the eldest son at their house.  [Music] They
also said that if we go to the wedding, they will let us watch the match in their neighborhood as a bonus.   All
this fun aside,
food and
accommodation can be a big problem when traveling through small villages.  For such
people, [music] such families are a God-given
gift.  Maybe it has nothing to do with the states, it has nothing to do
with the past. I think
people everywhere are full of love and affection. If
you have similar experiences, let me know in the comment
section.